# Gonzalo E. Loaiza

Social Media Strategist Director Creativo & Consultor at Wild Dream Peru Internacional Sales Mánager at Andina Outdoors

gonloaiza@gmail.com

# Summary

Experienced in Managing positions, Business Development and Sales in differente fields and years working in the marketing and advertising industry.

Prooven experience in Nonprofit Organizations.

Skilled in Negotiation and Business meetings, Strong Portuguese, Native Spanish and Certified English translator, Interpretar and Teacher.

Entrepreneur, Social Media Strategist, Business Planner and Wild Creator.

# Experience

## **International Sales Manager**

March 2016 - Present

#### **English Instructor, Translator & Interpreter**

June 2010 - Present

#### Social Media Strategist, Consultor & Director Creativo

August 2014 - Present

#### **Traductor Externo**

February 2014 - Present

Recepcion y envio de documentos en el ambito minero, para su traduccion literal del idioma Espanol al Ingles.

#### **Director Fundador**

June 2012 - Present

Starting a new business endeavor focused on quality in customer service, hospitality, entertainment, campaign events, Business improvements related to optimization of processes and well-instructed personnel.

#### **English Advisor**

May 2013 - December 2013 (8 months)

Teach, guide and advise students into their english learning process and provide extra curricular sessions in pronunciation and conversation skills.

#### **Ejecutivo de Cuentas**

March 2012 - December 2012 (10 months)

FramePost. Dream Animation Studio. Animation & digital post production studio.

Captación y Manejo De Cuentas.

## **Paralegal Assistant**

November 2009 - March 2010 (5 months)

A loan modification, debt settlement, and bankruptcy company working directly with the law firm of KRAMER & Department of the KRAMER & Department of the company working directly with the law firm

Keep accurate files of all documents received and generated.

In charge of handle documentation, draft contracts and agreements.

In charge of translation of all documents.

Assist customers with financial hardship situations and help them to find a solution.

#### **Administrative Assistant**

June 2008 - February 2010 (1 year 9 months)

NATIONAL HISPANIC UNIVERSITY. A Non-Profit Pre-school for the Hispanic community.

Keep accurate files of all documents received and generated.

Enter student data, attendance and schedules into system.

Assist in student registration and related processes for the institution.

Evaluate and resolve student inquiries.

Generate Fiscal Forms and Contracts with California Department of Education

## **Assistant Law Firm - Legal Representative**

July 2006 - April 2007 (10 months)

In charge of negotiations with home/farm owners, legal advise, and get licenses grants thru lawful requisites in City Halls; working in teams with specialist in different areas related to Engineering where I was the legal agent, chosen for the Legal Firm, of the southern region of Peru for a National Expansion Project of the biggest telecommunication Company at that time; called MOVISTAR. Successfully accomplishing all tasks and duties assigned to me.

#### Law Intern

June 2005 - July 2006 (1 year 2 months)

Client TELEFONICA MOVILES S.A.A., Telecommunications Company

Agent/Legal Representative of Client focused on Administrative expansion issues.

Direct Negotiation with City Halls and Municipalities.

In charge of compliance with licensing requirements.

Direct negotiations with Home Owners and Rural Properties owners.

In charge of "Expansion project" with engineers' team thru the Southern Peru to close Leasing/Licensing deals.

# Education

## The National Hispanic University

Translation & Interpretation Certified Program, English - Spanish, 2009 - 2010

## UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN EAU CLAIRE & VIA LINGUA LATIN AMERICA

Certification, Teaching English as a Second or Foreign Language/ESL Language Instructor, 2014 - 2014

## City College of San Francisco

International Business, 2009 - 2011

### **Universidad Catolica San Pablo**

Law School, Law, 2004 - 2007

### **IEBS**

Master's Degree, Marketing Online, Estrategia Digital y Social Media, 2015

### Universidad Católica de Santa María

Studies, Publicidad y Multimedia, 2015

Colegio San Jose

# Gonzalo E. Loaiza

Social Media Strategist Director Creativo & Consultor at Wild Dream Peru Internacional Sales Mánager at Andina Outdoors

gonloaiza@gmail.com



Contact Gonzalo E. on LinkedIn